{
    "id": "13aa0bf7faf245389da4cf3b5f22d2f5",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have not been well ……………….. I returned from Bangkok.",
            "description": "We use since to reckon from a point of time in the past.",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did he see the policeman …………………. he disappeared.",
            "description": "We use than after no sooner.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone rose to their feet ……………………… the chief guest entered the room.",
            "description": "We can use ‘as’ to talk about two events that happen simultaneously.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "while",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t talk ………………………… she is singing.",
            "description": "We can use while to introduce a longer background action which is going on when something else happens.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "since",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… I get older, I get happier.",
            "description": "As is often used with simple tenses to talk about situations that develop / change together.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Because",
                "When"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ordered to wait ……………………….. the signal was given.",
            "description": "Till indicates time. Unless indicates a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "till",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Write it down …………………….. you should forget about it.",
            "description": "Lest can introduce an adverb clause of purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "lest",
                "because",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They spoke in a low voice ……………………….. the child wouldn’t wake up.",
            "description": "So that can indicate the purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He thinks that he can buy justice ………………………. he is rich.",
            "description": "We use because to indicate the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not pay ………………………. he sends me the bill again.",
            "description": "Unless indicates a condition. It is similar to if not.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. I had not seen this with my own eyes, I would not have believed it.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Had"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. you are very clever, you should be able to solve this puzzle.",
            "description": "Since indicates the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "For",
                "Hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}